

# DO PHUONG GIANG

As a fourth-year student majoring in Accounting and Auditing, I am always driven by a passion for continuously learning professional in my field as well as develop my social knowledge. With strengths such as meticulousness, proficiency with Microsoft Office, Misa and SAP softwares along with my determination with learning and working, I believe that I can accumulate valuable experience and bring value to the company.

Phone: 0383959758

**Email:** dophuonggiang1206@gmail.com

Location: Ho Chi Minh city

## **EDUCATION**

# HO CHI MINH BANKING OF UNIVERSITY ACCOUNTING AND AUDITING 2021 - 2024

- Bachelor program
- Semi-English program

Accumulated GPA: 3.0/4.0

## **CERTIFICATES**

- IELTS 6.0 OVERALL
- MOS EXCEL 935/100
- MOS WORD 962/1000
- MOS POWERPOINT 892/1000

#### SKILLS

- Proficiency with Microsoft Office, Misa and SAP
- Proficiency in English communication
- Presentation
- Leadership
- Teamwork

# **ACTIVITIES**

LEADER OF THE ARTICLE WORKSHOP: THE DEVELOPMENT OF DIGITAL TRANSFORMATION TECHNOLOGY IN FINANCIAL AND BANKING MANAGEMENT

#### FEB 2024 - MARCH 2024

- Organizing meetings and delegating tasks among members
- Tracking plans and evaluating progress
- Preparing content and presentation slides
- Representing the team in presenting and answering questions

Learning points: Planning, Critical thinking,

Team management

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# ACCOUNTING INTERN WESTLAKE COMPOUNDS VIETNAM OCT 2024 - NOW

- Checking documents and running payments
- · Collecting and arranging bank, VAT documents
- · Debt reconciliation
- Inventorying and supporting for closing entries
- · Liaising with bank for payments

**Learning points:** Payment run, Connecting with external corporations, SAP software

# JUNIOR AUSTRALIAN ACCOUNTANT SEAMLESS OUTSOURCING SEPTEMBER 2024

- Collecting and arranging documents from the clients
- Checking documents and recording data in the software
- Preparing financial reports and working papers based on client requirements
- Gaining knowledge and practicing doing job about SMSF

**Learning points:** Accuracy and Meticulousness, Financial reports preparation, Data entry and Management

# ACCOUNTING INTERN DONG NAI JOINT STOCK COMPANY OF AGRICULTURAL MATERIAL JULY 2024 - AUGUST 2024

- Assisting the accounting department in collecting and entering raw data into the Accounting SQL and MISA software
- Checking and reconciling recorded figures with invoices and bank documents
- Controlling and following AR and AP of B2B customer

**Learning points:** Basic knowledge about Accounting software, Reconciliation and Verification